so in this meditation we're going to
practice something
uh we'll
go through some of the death experience
and then we'll reach the crystal
and we'll spend some time on emptiness
and then we'll reach the part where we
say
that's
me is
tamakaya
which is the
dharma body okay
and uh
it's very cool
if you reach the dharma body at
okay
then uh
at 8 30 and one second
your your uh
paradise body is comes out
okay with those five qualities
okay
the first quality is what
certainty
yeah you have this marks okay 112 marks
if you're coming to kamala sheila we're
going to read them very
carefully we're going to do them very
carefully i never heard anybody teach
all of them
it's it'll be very nice okay
uh
and i finished the text last night late
last night so
uh
let's uh
i just say that because the chinese team
has to translate it
it's 40 pages okay
all right
and that'll be fun
so
so we're going to practice
that special moment
okay
that's me
i'm in the body
okay like that it's very
the minute you reach
that's me
then the next minute
then you're like wow
okay paradise body
then
earth body is any time
after that you're like
i think i'll wait till nine o'clock
to go to los angeles
to help somebody you know like that
that's a different decision
but
in this meditation
i want you to we're gonna go through the
death
to the crystal
then we're gonna
be inside the crystal and do four things
and then
we're gonna look at the dharma body and
say
oh that's me and then
then practice this uh
these signs okay i want you to start
with
two sides okay one is here
dharma wheel okay
and it's not a tattoo
it's uh three-dimensional
you know it's bump you know it comes up
okay like that but not
creepy
it's still nice to hold their hand
okay it's not like holding a
cow's hand or something
it feels not their hand is also
the softest
so the it's you can feel the mark here
if you close your eyes you can feel it
but it's very soft okay
both hands
if you want you can do both feet
actually there's four
okay and there's many signs one on the
neck one on the chest different ones
i'll show you later okay
uh
okay so then at the same time
we're gonna call it's called zuppu okay
here
then uh
it's a little bump here okay silver
color
okay looks like silver
and not very big like
like olive they say olive size
okay half a hour
and then uh just practice that it's very
beautiful okay like that's where those
indian women wear this
there's a
chi
there's a chakra here and there's a
tig there's a bindu
there's a in the chakra there's a drop
and
so i want you to practice those two
you already have a drop there
you already have something there
some people get a mole here or something
that's very lucky
one woman in this
group had a baby and
in czechoslovakia it has a big
thing right here that's a good sign okay
very good sign
okay so
it's already you have some
thing here
so when you focus here during this
meditation
it should change your concentration you
should feel different
and if you want you can breathe through
here
okay and that's a good practice all
right
so we're gonna go through the death
process
reach the dharmabaya body
say that's me and then
it takes half a second like boom
and then you're like wow
cool
better than tattoo
okay
then you can feel it because you're
going to have it so
you know
everybody knows the future a little bit
and you already feel something on your
head
and i just want you to
get used to it okay and it will help you
become a buddha okay
and don't forget this one and then this
one okay here we go you ready
okay
blow your nose again
uh
okay then you are walking across this
land
and in the distance you can see a mirage
slowly walk towards it
so
very close now to the mirage
and then through the mirage
and then on the other side you're
surrounded by
smoke
still walking
so
and then suddenly you see sparks in the
smoke
as you walk
and
then
a clear
a still flame
kind of limb
and you're walking towards it
and it's getting bigger and bigger
and your mind is getting smaller and
smaller
so
then you walk through the candle flame
and on the other side
it's dark but at the horizon you can see
daylight starting to
show on daybreak
and you keep walking towards it
it's very quiet
so
and soon the day breaks around you
the sky is white
and you're still walking
and there's a red color
on the horizon like a sunset
and you're walking towards that
and then you're surrounded in red
keep walking
and then everything's plugged
then go put more blood deeper plug
very silent very quiet
deeper blowing
and
as though at the end of a very long
tunnel
everything becomes crystalline
just clear and crystal
then you
think
how much of this is coming from me
did the mirage come from me
did the smoke come from me
is it all coming out of seeds in my mind
pictures
coming out of seeds in my mind
so
uh
how much is not coming out of pictures
in my mind
[Music]
and then there should be nothing
that's more crystalline deeper crystal
and you understand this is emptiness
higher
reality
it feels hard
it feels above
how many things don't come from me
and super quiet
on this
all your
chakras are open
the chi is moving
very
smoothly in the middle channel
and you feel
extremely happy
and the emptiness you understand it very
clearly
and then you say if i could become that
i would be a buddha
and i could really help people
in many worlds
all of them
so i will i will be this emptiness
and then in that moment
you feel on your hands
the body changes
and some wheels come on your hand down
the wheel aids boat
and enjoy the feeling
the wheels are part of your skin
and then on your forehead
trying to find the spot
where there's a lot of pronoun qi
you can
try in different places on your forehead
focus
on different places
should be
between your eyebrows
up
about an
inch centimeter
and
sometimes it helps to go into your skull
maybe a few millimeters maybe half an
inch
see if you can find the spot
and imagine a
silver
half a silver boulder like a other
and i'd like you to breathe through this
ball so
the breath is coming
not through the nose
but through the forehead
and we'll relax here for a few minutes
that's the last thing
and
just
breathe
through your forehead
sometimes
feel the wheels on your hands
so
um
then please come to your breath three
deep breaths
each out breath
try to share this good karma with other
people
and then you can silly open your eyes
take a stretch